<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>Por Fazer</title>
    
    
    <description>Por Fazer</description>
    
    <link>https://dielsonsales.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://dielsonsales.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Starting a new blog</title>
        <description>
          Or writing as a learning tool - 
          It’s been a while since I last wrote blog posts and after reading a nice post about this, I feel like it’s time to get back on track researching and posting summaries of things that I’ve learned recently. It’s also worth noting that with the rise of ChatGPT it’s been...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://dielsonsales.github.io/2023-05-11-starting-a-new-blog/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dielsonsales.github.io/2023-05-11-starting-a-new-blog/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My List of Interesting and Important Git Configurations</title>
        <description>
          
          Since I use git daily on my job and also on personal projects and experiments, I’m compiling here some nice configuration options and tricks that will help not just me but also anyone who stumble upon this article. It’s important to note this is an ongoing article I’ll be updating...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 23:51:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://dielsonsales.github.io/2022-12-22-list-git-configs/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dielsonsales.github.io/2022-12-22-list-git-configs/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Installing an Oracle Database for the first time</title>
        <description>
          
          In this article, I mean to document my journey planning, installing and deploying an Oracle database for the first time. Learning this was a requirement to do some projects in my database classes in college, so it’ll be useful to document things here while it’s still fresh in my mind....
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 18:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://dielsonsales.github.io/2022-12-10-installing-oracle-database-for-the-first-time/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dielsonsales.github.io/2022-12-10-installing-oracle-database-for-the-first-time/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Writing a minimalist Android client, part 1</title>
        <description>
          
          So I was reading recently a nice article called “The small web is beautiful” which got me inspired to take this concept to Android apps. For a long time already, I’ve used Boost to read posts on Reddit and I wanted to build something similar that would make reading comments...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 15:35:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://dielsonsales.github.io/2021-03-07-minimalist-android-app/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dielsonsales.github.io/2021-03-07-minimalist-android-app/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sample blog post</title>
        <description>
          Each post also has a subtitle - 
          This is a demo post to show you how to write blog posts with markdown. I strongly encourage you to take 5 minutes to learn how to write in markdown - it’ll teach you how to transform regular text into bold/italics/headings/tables/etc. Here is some bold text Here is a secondary...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://dielsonsales.github.io/2020-02-28-test-markdown/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dielsonsales.github.io/2020-02-28-test-markdown/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flake it till you make it</title>
        <description>
          Excerpt from Soulshaping by Jeff Brown - 
          Under what circumstances should we step off a path? When is it essential that we finish what we start? If I bought a bag of peanuts and had an allergic reaction, no one would fault me if I threw it out. If I ended a relationship with a woman who...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>https://dielsonsales.github.io/2020-02-26-flake-it-till-you-make-it/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dielsonsales.github.io/2020-02-26-flake-it-till-you-make-it/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
